One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Justice Will Prevail!!
Hurry to the execution platform!
The Giant Squad is coming!
They're targeting Little Oars Jr.!
Stopping that thing...
... is our duty!
His size is unbelievable...
He's more than twice as large as any ordinary Giant!
Keep shooting!
He's only flesh and blood... he can't be invulnerable!
They brought one hell of an ally.
Fire! Shoot him down!
Oars! Forget about it!
Your size makes you too easy a target!
Ace-kun!
I'm coming for ya!
This is bad!
Stop him!
Oars opened a path into the bay!
Invade the bay!
Plaza
The Seven
Warlords
Oars
Fall back! Fortify the shoreline!
Don't let them reach the plaza!
I've never had to look up at someone before!
You said it!
This is as far as you get!
Vice Admiral Lacroix!
That Oars... No point trying to hold him back...
There's a difference between being a hero and throwing your life away!
Old Man, please don't stop me!
I wanna save 'im!
I wanna save Ace-kun as fast as possible!
I hear ya.
Men! Wipe your asses!
Let's give Oars some support!
Yeah!
How do we fight a guy this big?!
How dare you hurt Vice Admiral Lacroix!
If you get distracted by Oars, I'll take you down!
H-Hey! Guys!
The Pirate Empress, I'm guessing?
My body's... crumbling?!
Hey! What do you think you're doing, attacking marines?!
I agreed to fight against Whitebeard...
but I never said I would be your ally.
Whether enemies or friends, all men are the same!
All but one man...
I want to leave here with my promise fulfilled.
What are you saying?!
Can you forgive this beauty?
Y-You...!
You!
I'll save ya now!
Oars...
Oars!
That's enough! Stop this!
You won't make it this far!
Me?
I learned how to make it in the Wano Country.
Try it on!
Ace-san burned the darn thing twice trying to make that hat.
A fire man like him shouldn't be weaving straw.
Whoa! It's much cooler now!
Really? Great!
Aim for Oars!
Oars!
I guess there was no chance.
He's such a big target!
Captain Oars!
What are you doing outside?
Hmm... I don't even get wet by the rain...
It's really sturdy.
This is great!
At the very least...
Even if it's just one of the Warlords...
Is something wrong, demon?
My legs won't...
Captain!
Captain! Why are you outside again?
The snow doesn't even reach me.
I'm not cold at all!
This is really good!
Thanks, Ace-
How fun!
Oars!
I-It's the monster!
He's breached the plaza!
Just a little more...
Just a little further to Ace-kun...
That Doflamingo bastard!
He's gone and cut off a leg!
Even though I said I wanted the corpse...
Go!
Oars!
Look! This is the right way to kill someone!
Captain Oars!
Damn the Seven Warlords!
Captain!
Oars!
If I use his corpse, I can create the ultimate zombie warrior!
Oars...
You're wide open, Whitebeard!
Vice Admiral Ronse!
H-He beat a Giant -
and a Navy HQ vice admiral at that - effortlessly!
Charge across Oars!
Marineford - Inside the Bay
This is priceless!
Doflamingo! How could you do that to Oars?!
I won't let you get away with this!
What's so funny?!
You wanna know what's so funny?
This feeling of being right at the center of an era, that's what!
This is the turning point!
Quit spouting nonsense!
Just as I'd expect of the commander!
Doflamingo is running away from him!
Impossible! This is just too much for me!
I'm too scared to do anything!
So many strong people are falling, one after another!
There's nothing I can do here!
Someone like me can't...
Wait, Koby! If you're running away, then I'm coming with you!
Return to the battlefield!
Let me go! Please!
It's Admiral Akainu! What's he doing here?
I'm afraid of dying! When I think of my family, I can't even move!
Please! I'm begging you! Please!
We marines...
fight against pirates and carry the justice of the world on our backs.
Someone who runs away and lets an enemy see his back...
has no right to call himself a marine!
Someone like that is merely...
trash!
If you truly cared for your family,
you wouldn't have disgraced them like this!
N-No way! How could he do that to an ally?
Admiral Sakazuki! We've finished preparing for the operation.
Have you now? Finally!
Operation?
Ace!
Commander Atmos!
Why...
My body's not listening to me...
Stop this, Doflamingo!
Pirates are evil? The Navy is righteous?
Those views change as often as the tides!
Kids who've never known peace have different values from those who've never known war.
It's the job of those at the top to
decide what's good and what's evil.
This place is the turning point.
Justice will triumph, you say?
Why of course!
Because the winners will become justice!
Marineford - Bay Head
Don't let them close the path Oars has opened!
Advance into the bay!
An icebreaker?
It's the Ice Witch, Whitey Bay!
Nothing to it.
Now, all of you! Let's go!
Thanks!
Come on, men! Forward, into the bay!
The bay's been breached in two spots!
The Whitebeard Pirates and their allies are surging through both openings,
and they're attacking the bay in large numbers, Fleet Admiral Sengoku!
That's not a problem.
What?
Tsuru-san, commence the operation.
Marineford - Bay Head
At last.
Move it! Or you'll be more than just wounded!
Move it, old woman!
I've been washed!
I've been hung out to dry!
But it feels so nice!
You're a million years too young to stand a chance against me.
Calling all ships and all men!
You're planning something, aren't you?
The Resourceful General, Sengoku the Buddha.
Gramps!
Why have you come here? Do you wish to protest against my plan?
No, we're up against pirates. There's no room for sympathy.
Then...
Be silent!
You don't mind, right?
I'm just gonna sit here.
You idiot! You too?!
Don't hit Luffy, you damn geezer!
"Damn"?!
Ace, how dare you?!
I have no sympathy for criminals...
but for my family, I do.
What... should I do?
Damn you Ace! Why couldn't you just live as I told you?!
Ace...
You two are gonna become strong marines.
You got that?
You're gonna become strong marines.
Gramps...!
If you cause some sort of commotion here, I won't show you any mercy, Garp.
If I was gonna do something, I'd have done it already.
Did you hear their plan just now, Helmeppo-san?
Yeah...
They're gonna ignore Fire Fist Ace's scheduled execution time and just kill him now!
If they do that...
What's that?
Is that...?
Something's falling out of the sky!
Is it a sneak attack from the Whitebeard Pirates?
I knew you'd overdo it!
This is all because of his wink.
Vyou're blaming this on vme, Croco?!
Who cares?! We're gonna die!
The sea beneath us is frozen solid!
Oh! I'm made of rubber, so I'll be fine!
Then you'll be the only survivor!
We have to do something!
Vi don't want to die like this!
Someone, stop vus!
I never should've listened to you, Straw Hat!
Dammit!
Ace!
Editing, Sewil
Quality Assurance, Galaxy 9000, Pepperjack
Karaoke & Attack Effects, KaitouYahiko
Timing, Sewil
Soundtracking, Halee
Translation, Yibis
Raw Provider, Cruchyroll